Guide to the Charles Hobson Collection, 1985-2008 M1555
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XXIX. Writing on the Body, 1999
  - Subseries B. Proofs and Plates, Centolella, Tom; Collins, Billy; DeMerritt, John; Evans, Kathy; Levy, Harriet Lane; Lopez, Barry; Mann, Charmetta; Shaw, Alice; Twain, Mark, 1835-1910; Wilbur, Richard
    - #1 Mystery, 3 plastic sleeves with 2 trial proofs and 3 plates, plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Alternate Plate #12 (Box 41, Items 1, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #11; Trial Proof; transparency and Kodalith; color notes and inking note (Box 41, Items 1, Sleeve 3)
    - #2 Proportions, 4 plastic sleeves containing 9 trial proofs, 3 trial plates and 1 final plate plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #3: 2 Trial Proofs: transparency and 2 Kodaliths; color notes and inking notes (Box 41, Items 2, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #4: 3 Trial Proofs; color notes and inking notes (Box 41, Items 2, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #1: 2 Trial Proofs (Box 41, Items 2, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #2: 2 Trial Proofs; Photogravure Gradient Strip; color notes and inking notes (Box 41, Items 2, Items 4)
    - #3 What Use, 6 plastic sleeves with 8 trial proofs and 5 plates, plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate Unnumbered: Trial Proof (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #2: Trial Proof (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #13A: Trial Proof (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #15: Trial Proof; Photogravure Gradient Strip (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 4)
      - Plate #14 (unnumbered on plate): Trial Proof; color notes and inking notes (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 5)
      - 3 Trial Proofs: transparencies and 2 Kodaliths; color notes and inking notes [NO PLATE] (Box 41, Items 3, Sleeve 6)
    - #4 Turning, 5 plastic sleeves with 4 trial proofs and 4 plates, plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #18A: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 4, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #18: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 4, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #17: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 4, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #16: Trial Proof; Photogravure Gradient Strip (Box 42, Items 4, Sleeve 4)
      - Transparencies and 2 Kodaliths: color notes and inking notes [NO PLATE] (Box 42, Items 4, Sleeve 5)
    - #5 Again, 8 plastic sleeves with 6 trial proofs and 6 plates, plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #26A: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #26B: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #26: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #25: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 4)
      - Alternate Plate #24: Trial Proof; color notes and inking notes (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 4)
      - Alternate Plate #26C: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 6)
      - transparencies and 2 Kodaliths: etching notes [NO PLATES] (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 7)
      - color notes and inking notes [NO PLATES] (Box 42, Items 5, Sleeve 8)
    - #6 Contour, 5 plastic sleeves with 4 trial proofs and 4 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #22: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 6, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #22A (unnumbered on plate): Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 6, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #23: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 6, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #23: Trial Proof (Box 42, Items 6, Sleeve 4)
      - transparencies and Kodalith: color notes and inking notes [NO PLATES] (Box 42, Items 6, Sleeve 5)
    - #7 Essential, 4 plastic sleeves with 2 trial proofs and 3 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Trial Proof #9: transparencies and Kodalith; color notes and inking notes [NO PLATE] (Box 43, Items 7, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #9A: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items 7, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #10: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items 7, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate Unnumbered (Box 43, Items 7)
    - #8 Artifice, 2 plastic sleeves with 2 trial proofs and 2 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #5: Trial Proof; transparency and Kodalith; color notes and inking notes (Box 43, Items 8, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #6: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items 8, Sleeve 2)
    - Alternative Image A, 3 plastic sleeves with 3 trial proofs and 3 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes.
      - Plate #21: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items A, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #20: Trial Proof; transparency and Kodalith (Box 43, Items A, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #19: Trial Proof; color notes and inking notes (Box 43, Items A, Sleeve 3)
    - Alternative Image B: 6 plastic sleeves with 5 trial proofs and 5 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #29B: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 1)
      - Alternate Plate #29A: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #29: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #28: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 4)
      - Alternate Plate #27: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 5)
      - transparencies and Kodaliths: color notes and inking notes [NO PLATE] (Box 43, Items B, Sleeve 6)
    - Alternative Image C, 4 plastic sleeves with 3 trial proofs and 3 plates plus transparency, color notes, and inking notes
      - Plate #7: Trial Proof; Photogravure Gradient Strip; color notes and inking notes (Box 43, Items C, Sleeve 1)
      - transparencies and Kodalith [NO PLATE] (Box 43, Items C, Sleeve 2)
      - Alternate Plate #8A: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items C, Sleeve 3)
      - Alternate Plate #8: Trial Proof (Box 43, Items C, Sleeve 4)